Web developer

Throughout my academic journey, I have gained in-depth knowledge and practical skills in various aspects of web development, including front-end and back-end technologies, responsive design, and user experience optimization. Additionally, my active involvement in clubs has sharpened my communication, collaboration, and problem-solving abilities, making me an effective team player in web development projects.

khawlaselmi195@gmail.com

- Post Box 197, Mornaguia Manouba
- 52 865 171

DATABASE skills

SOI

MongoDB

PL/SQL

•••••

Programming languages

MERN Stack

✓ MongoDB ✓ Express JS✓ React JS ✓ Node JS

JavaScript

• • • • • • •

_ _

•••••

~#

•••••

Java

Methodologies

Scrum

Soft Skills

Listening skills, Autonomy, Team work, Presentation Skills, Adabtability, Problem-solving

Interests

Reading, Digital Painting

Social networks

in @khawla-selmi-045b81174

Education

MASTER DEGREE IN MEDIA ENGINEERING: WEB DEVELOPMENT

From September 2021 to June 2024

Higher Institute of Arts and Multimedia Manouba, Tunisia

BACHELOR DEGREE IN COMMUNICATION AND MULTIMEDIA

From September 2018 to June 2021

Higher Institute of Arts and Multimedia Manouba, Tunisia

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA IN MATHEMATICS

From September 2017 to June 2018 Al Farabi Mornaguia Manouba, Tunisia

Work experience

End of studies project internship : College La fontaine

From February 2021 to May 2021 College "La fontaine" Ariana

Developing a High school platform with its backend:

This plateform allows:

*Streamline communication and collaboration among students, parents and teachers.

- *Provide online courses.
- *Take online tests
- *Sharing school activities.
- *Online purchases of various school supplies
- *Club registration
- *High school registration

Methodology: V model

Environement: JavaSript, PHP, Boostrap, HTML.

Voluntary experience

Member

September 2022 AMAVI Campus Manouba Insaniyyat Tunis 2022 Forum.

VP RF

Since November 2021 Tunivisions Fondation Tunis

Presiden

From January 2018 to January 2022 CultuClub ISAMM Manouba

Languages

English

Aptis Certification C

French

•••••

Advanced

Spanish

•••••

Basic